Guide to the Donald Clifford Gallup Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- April 2001 Acquisition, 1866-2000; 14; 78.5; (87 boxes) + 4 record album storage, 4 art, 1 object storage
  - Correspondence and Subject Files
    - Day, Worden, 1954-1986, undated
    - Denson, Alan, 1962-1967, undated
    - De Vane, undated
    - De Vito (empty folder), undated
    - Devrim, Shirin, 1948 June 15
    - Dickinson, Donald C., circa 1968-2000
    - Dietrich, Marlene, 1967, undated
    - Dix, George, 1947-1999
    - Dreier, Katherine S., 1950-1952, undated
    - Drew, Elizabeth, 1949 March 11
    - Duberman, Martin, 1983-1989
    - Duncan, Ronald, 1966-1980
    - Duncan, Rudolph, 1981-1988
    - Dunham, William H., 1946-1983
    - Durrell, Lawrence, 1963-1988, undated
    - Duschnes, Philip C., 1940-1969
    - Duval, K. D., 1964
    - Dydo, Ulla, 1981-2000, undated; 3
    - Dzwonkoski, Peter, 1974-2000, undated; 2
    - "E" General, 1937-1990
    - Eakins Press, 1974-1998 (Box 34)
    - Edelstein, Mel, 1957-1996, undated
    - Edwards, John, 1954-1958
    - Einstein, William, 1952
    - Eisenhower, Dwight, undated
    - Eisler, Benita & Colin, 1986-1992
    - Eliot, Ada, 1936-1961
    - Eliot, Charles W., undated
    - Eliot, Charlotte C., undated
    - Eliot, Henry W., Jr., 1936-1947, undated; 3
    - Eliot, Teresa G., 1945-1980; 3
    - Eliot, T. S.
      - Correspondence of Donald Gallup regarding T. S. Eliot
        - Booksellers
          - "A - Z" General, 1936-1998, undated
          - Charles E. Tuttle Company, 1946-1967
          - Firuski, Maurice, 1937-1971
          - Gekoski, R. A., 1990-1996
          - Glenn Horowitz Bookseller, 1990-1994, undated; 2
          - M & S Rare Books, Inc., 1970, undated
        - Individuals
          - "A - C" General, circa 1963-1987
          - Baillargeon, Joseph C., 1989-1999, undated; 2
          - Baker, William, 1985-1992
          - Bradshaw, David, 1994-1995
          - Crawford, Robert, 1983-1988
          - "D - G" General, 1949-1997, undated
          - Flores, Angel, 1937 January 26
          - Gardner, Helen, 1973, undated
          - Gordon, Lyndall, 1973, undated (Box 35)
          - "H - L" General, 1959-1992
          - Hooker, Joan F., 1980-1988
          - Huisman, David A., 1966-1974, undated
          - Husain, Rizwan, 1966-1970
          - Kajima, Sho, 1951-1956, undated
          - "M - N" General, 1950-1991
          - Marathe, Sudhakar, 1980-1982
          - Margolis, John D., 1966-1973, undated
          - Matthews, T. S., 1970-1972
          - McCue, Jim, 1988-1997
          - McElderry, B. R., 1969-1970
          - Meekin, J. R., 1979-2000
          - Newton-De Molina, David, 1975
          - "O - R" General, 1947-1994
          - Onodera, Takeshi, 1959-1967
          - Packard, Frederick C., 1949, undated
          - Ricks, Christopher, 1993-1999
          - Rylands, George H. W., 1988
          - "S" General, 1947-1999
          - Schmidt, Gerd, 1966-1993, undated
          - Schuchard, Ronald, 1970-1993, undated
          - Scott, Peter Dale, 1985 November 27
          - Sodums, Dzintars, 1993
          - "T - Z" General, 1974-1980
          - Tirumalai, C. K., 1972, undated
        - Libraries
          - "A - Z" General, 1969-1988
          - British Library, undated
          - King's College Library, Cambridge, 1987-1990, undated
          - New York Public Library, 1958-1968
          - Richards, Eliot, 1988 September 19
        - Publishers
          - "A - D" General, 1946-1968
          - Christopher Helm, Publisher Limited, 1990, undated
          - The Classical Association, 1986
          - "E - H" General, 1946-1968
          - H. M. V., 1947-1949
          - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc., 1964-1970
          - "I - M" General, 1937-1974
          - Nin, Anaïs, 1951 June 22
          - "N - P" General, 1936-1969
          - "Q - Z" General, 1933-1997
          - Virgil Society, 1951 July 3
      - Transcripts, photostats, and photocopies of T. S. Eliot correspondence
        - "A - Z" General, undated; 2
        - Baker, Denys Val, 1958 (Box 36)
        - Benet, William Rose, undated
        - Bennett, Arnold, undated
        - Bookman, undated
        - Brocklebank, Mrs., undated
        - Brooks, Cleanth, undated
        - Brooks, Van Wyck, undated
        - Buss, Ms., undated
        - Canby, Henry S., undated
        - Childe, Godfrey, undated
        - Cobden-Sanderson, Richard, undated; 3
        - Delaney, Cyril, undated
        - DeVane, William C., undated
        - The Dial, undated
        - Eeckels, Guido, undated
        - Eliot, Henry, undated
        - Evans, D. W., undated
        - Firuski, Maurice, undated
        - Fitts, Dudley, undated
        - Ford, Madox, undated
        - Friede, Donald, undated
        - Furioso, undated
        - Gallup, Donald, undated; 3
        - Gardner, Mrs., undated
        - Gervais, Terence White, undated
        - Gregory, Alyse, undated
        - Hayward, John, undated
        - Heap, Jane, undated
        - Heggem, Melvile, undated
        - Horgan, Paul, undated
        - "The Hound and Horn", undated
        - Hudson, Cyril, undated
        - Jepson, Edgar, undated
        - Kristol, Irving, undated
        - Lewis, Wyndham, undated
        - McAlmon, Robert, undated
        - Martz, Louis L., undated
        - Maurras, Charles, undated
        - Meyerstein, E. H. W., undated
        - Miłosz, Czesław, undated
        - Monro, Alida, undated
        - Monro, Harold, undated
        - Monroe, Ms., undated
        - The Nation, undated
        - Ôtake, Masaru, undated
        - Owlett, F. C., undated
        - Parker, Derek, undated
        - Patmore, Brigit, undated
        - Perkins, Edith, undated; 7
        - Phelps, William Lyon, undated
        - Pope, John, undated
        - Porteous, Hugh Gordon, undated
        - Potts, Paul, undated
        - Pound, Ezra, undated
        - Putnam, H. Phelps, undated
        - Robinson, C. U. P., undated
        - Rodker, John, undated
        - Russell, Bertrand, undated
        - Seymour, Ralph Fletcher, undated
        - Shapiro, Karl, undated
        - Shaw, Walter Hanks, undated
        - Shorter, Mr., undated
        - Singer, John (empty folder), undated
        - Smyth, Charles H., undated
        - Stead, W. T., undated
        - Stein, Gertrude, undated
        - Thayer, Ellen, undated
        - Thompson, Margaret, undated
        - "The Tiger's Eye", undated (Box 37)
        - Tinker, Mr., undated
        - Wells, James, undated
        - Wilson, Edmund, undated
        - Wilson, T. C., undated
        - Wolff, Kurt, undated
        - Yale, undated
        - Yale Poetry Review, undated
        - Yale Review, undated
        - Zukovsky, Louis, undated
        - 1937 Catalogue, 1937-1938, undated
        - Memorial Fund, 1966-1988
        - Review, 1975, undated
        - Bolo Poems, etc., undated
    - Eliot, Valerie, 1965-1999, undated; 3
    - Eliot College, 1983, undated
    - Elizabethan Club, 1967-1997, undated
    - Ellman, Richard, 1962-1964, undated
    - Emerson, Judd, 1949
    - England, 1988 September
    - Enters, Angna, 1953-1989
    - Epstein, Jacob, 1964-1975, undated
    - Espey, John, 1965-1971
    - Europe, 1937-1988; 18
    - Europe
      - General Europe, 1989-2000; 12 (Box 38)
      - Greece, 1969
      - Knoxville, 1985-1998; 4
      - Plaza Travel, 1966, undated
      - Travel, 2000
      - Zermatt, 1999
    - Everett, Patricia, 1985-1995
    - "F" General, 1947-1990
    - Faber & Faber, Ltd. Publishers, 1935-1988; 8
    - Faust, Beatrix, 1990-1996, undated (Box 39)
    - Fellheimer, Jeannette, 1952-1969
    - Ficke, Gladys, 1961-1995
    - Fidelity, 1994
    - First Federal Bank, 1995 September 15
    - Fisher, Vardis, 1968
    - Flaccus, Kimball, 1953-1968
    - Fletcher, Edward, 1949-1956
    - Floyd, Virginia, 1976-1988; 3
    - Foote, Edward, 1980-1981
    - Foreign & International Book Company, Inc., 1946-1953
    - Forshan, Augusta, 1949-1979
    - Forum, 1977-1982
    - French, Robert D., 1947-1970, undated
    - Friar, Kimon, 1947
    - Fritz, Bernardine Szold, 1970-1981
    - Fulton, John & Lucia, 1937-1982
    - "G" General, 1953-1990, undated
    - Gallup, Donald
      - Biography, undated
      - Plainfield High School, 1930-1956, undated
      - Yale College, 1930-1937, undated; 4
      - Yale Graduate School, 1937-1994; 2
      - AdAmAn Club, 1942, undated
      - Southern Methodist University, 1937-1946, undated; 3
      - Service records, circa 1942-1944; 2
      - Burrowes, Elizabeth, 1945 (Box 40)
      - Buckingham Palace, 1942-1943
      - U. S. propaganda leaflets dropped over Germany, 1940s
      - Army, 1941-1946; 2
      - Autobiography, 1937-1948, undated; 2
      - Bibliography, assignments, 1962-1994, undated; 5
      - Courses, 1946-1951, undated
      - Letters to the Coxes, 1959-1994, undated
      - Letters to the family, 1969-1994
      - Jana Lynn, 1982-1992
      - Living Will, 1989 September 21
      - Medicare, 1979-2000; 2
      - Social Security, 1978-1995, undated; 2
      - TIAA - CREF, circa 1980-1991
      - Yale University Health Services, 1998-1999; 2
      - Yale. Salary, 1941-1980
    - Gardner, Helen, 1945-1948
    - Garland Publishing Inc., 1983-1991
    - Gaudier, Brzeska, 1965, undated
    - Gibbs, Tam C., 1952
    - Gierow, Karl Ragnar, 1957-1970
    - Gilmour-White, G. G., 1943-1969
    - Gimbel, Richard, 1958-1968, undated
    - Giroux, Robert, 1964-1994
    - Goldstone, Richard, 1969-1999
    - Goldwasser, Tom, 1979-1996, undated
    - Goodspeed's Book Shop, 1935-1961
    - Goodwin, Will, 1991 September 5
    - Gordan, John D., 1968-1987
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1936-1962; 2 (Box 41)
    - Goulden, H. J., 1935-1937, undated
    - The Graduate Club Association, 1974-1995, undated
    - Grant, John, 1936-1965
    - Grassi, Carolyn, 1989-1994, undated
    - Graves, Robert, 1952, undated
    - Greene, Graham, 1966, undated
    - Grolier Club, 1948-1999; 7
    - Guest, Barbara, 1980-1991
    - Guggenheim, 1955-2000; 2
    - Guinness, Alec, 1950-1986
    - "H" General, 1951-2000
    - Haas, Robert Bartlett, 1940-1991, undated; 2
    - Hagstrom, Jack, 1976-1997
    - Haight, Gordon & Mary, 1985-1990, undated
    - Hale, Emily, 1937
    - Hall, Donald, 1950-1995, undated
    - Hall, Marshall, 1934-1986
    - Hamalian, Leo, 1951-1971 (Box 42)
    - Hamilton, Edward K., 1988-2000
    - Hamilton, George H., 1948-2000
    - Hamilton College, 1961-1992
    - Hanover Gallery, 1954-1965
    - Hapgood, Hutchins, 1947-1998
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company, Inc., 1936-1989, undated; 4
    - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1950-1977; 3
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1933-1998, undated; 9
    - Harvard, 1937-1999, undated; 7
    - Harvard Library Bulletin, 1984-1992, undated; 2
    - Harvard University Press, 1935-1969 (Box 43)
    - Haskell House, 1977-1978
    - Hayden, Parker, 1980-1987
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel, 1935-1936, undated
    - Hayward, John, 1937-1988, undated
    - Hedrick, Ella, undated
    - Heffer and Sons Limited, 1935-1966
    - Hemingway, Ernest, undated
    - Henderson, Archie, 1981-2000, undated; 10
    - Herron, Ima Honaker, 1958-1969 (Box 44)
    - Hersey, John, 1993
    - Hesse, Eva, 1964-1970
    - Heymann, C. David, 1977-1980, undated
    - Hidy, Lance, undated
    - Himes, Chester, 1985, undated
    - Hirschland, Ellen, 1983-1993, undated
    - Hobson, Anthony, 1983-1984
    - Hodson, Sara S., 1989
    - Hofer, Philip, 1947-1989, undated
    - Holdan Books Limited, 1966-1982
    - Holden, Reuben Andrus, 1995
    - Hollander, John, 1985
    - Holliday Bookshop, 1935-1936, undated
    - Hollings, Frank, 1948-1961
    - Holt, Nora D., 1952-1966
    - Homberger, Eric, 1968-1970
    - Hoover, Roland, 1994, undated
    - Horgan, Paul, circa 1966-1990
    - Hotchkiss, Bill, 1991
    - House of Books, 1936-1998
    - Howes, Barbara, circa 1961-1994
    - Hubbell, L. W., 1947
    - Hutchins, Patricia, 1967-1974
    - Hughes, Langston, 1963-1986
    - Hugnet, Georges, 1952-1961, undated
    - Hugo, Harold, 1977-1986, undated
    - Hulme, Kathryn, 1977-1987, undated
    - Humidifier, undated
    - Hutchins, Henry, 1937
    - "I" General, 1947-1982, undated
    - Indiana, Robert, 1967-1998
    - Indiana University, 1992-1995
    - "J" General, 1952-1993
    - Jackson, Esther, 1980-1986; 2 (Box 45)
    - Jackson, Rose H., 1954-1964
    - Jackson, William A., 1946-1952, undated
    - James F. Drake Inc., 1948-1950
    - James, Rebecca, 1967-1989, undated
    - Jörgensen, Paula & Terry, 1982-1988
    - John, Augustus, 1951-1973, undated
    - John Carter Brown Library, 1946-1997
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1995
    - Johnson, John, 1937-1959, undated
    - Johnson, James Weldon, 1965-1985, undated
    - Johnson, Richard Colles, 1961-1988
    - Jonathan Edwards College, 1947-1997, undated; 4
    - Jonathan Edwards Fellows, 1952-1999, undated; 12
    - Jones, David, 1975-1979; 2
    - Joyce, James, undated
    - Juel-Jensen, Bent, 1955 June 24
    - Justema, William, 1976-1987, undated
    - "K" General, circa 1967-1994 (Box 46)
    - Kahnweiler, Daniel - Henry, 1952-1987, undated; 2
    - Kahnweiler, Gustav, 1949-1955, undated
    - Kaplan, Moreson H., 1971-1983, undated
    - Katz, Leon, 1968-1975
    - Kauffer, McKnight, 1954, undated
    - Kavanagh, Peter, 1960, undated
    - Keller, William, 1994-1996
    - Kellner, Bruce, 1961-1988; 5
    - Kenner, Hugh, 1962-1973, undated
    - Kermani, David, 1976-1977, undated
    - Kerr, Chester, 1965-1996, undated
    - Keynes, Quentin, 1968-1988, undated
    - Kezerian, Steve, 1963
    - King, Michael, 1985-1988, undated
    - Kinney, Arthur F., 1966-2000, undated
    - Kirgo Books, 1952-1957, undated
    - Kirkpatrick, B. J., 1962-1984, undated
    - Kirkpatrick, Ralph, 1949-1950, undated
    - Kirschenbaum, David, 1994 January 21
    - Knight, Jere, 1990 July 11
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard, 1940-1973
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 1937-1981, undated; 3
    - Koenig, Michael E. D., undated
    - Kohn, S. van E., 1967-1980, undated
    - Kops Monahan Travel, undated
    - Kuehn, Bob & Janet, 1967-2000, undated (Box 47)
    - Kuester, Lew, 1983-1992, undated
    - "L" General, 1947-1998, undated
    - Ladd, W. P., Mrs., 1947-1957, undated
    - Lang, Cecil Y., 1952-2000, undated; 2
    - Laughlin, James, 1956-1997; 5
    - Laurans, Penelope, 1994
    - Laurence, Dan H., 1978
    - Laurencin, Marie, 1969, undated
    - Laurie Hill Limited, 1964
    - Lawrence, Frieda, 1951-1964
    - Lawrence, T. E., 1934 November 16
    - Lear, Edward, 1947-1973, undated; 3
      Includes photocopies and transcripts of letters, photographs, notes, and printed material.
    - Lear, Edward, 1950-1999, undated; 3 (Box 48)
      Includes Donald Gallup correspondence regarding Edward Lear.
    - Leiris, Michel, 1952-1988, undated
    - Lerman, Leo, 1994, undated
    - Lescher, Robert, 1962-1985
    - Levin, Richard C., 1997-2000
    - Lewis, C. S., undated
    - Lewis, Wilmarth, 1947-1975
    - Lewis, Wyndham, undated
    - Library of America, 1985-1996, undated
    - Liebert, Herman W., 1950-1994, undated
    - Lilly Library, Indiana University, 1977-1997, undated
    - Lindsay, Vachel, 1950, undated
    - Little Review, undated
    - Littlefield, Lester, 1969
    - Litz, A. Walton, 1983-1992, undated
    - Liveright, 1972
    - Livingston, Dorothy, 1965-1992, undated
    - Longenbach, James, 1984-1986
    - Loos, Anita, 1963 December 7
    - Lowell, Robert, undated
    - Lowe, Sue, 1975-2000
    - Ludington, Townsend, circa 1982-1998
    - Ludwig, Richard, 1967-1980, undated
    - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1987, undated
    - Lutz, Mark, 1968
    - Lynes, George Platt, 1951-1991
    - Lytton, Bernard, 1994-1997, undated
    - "M" General, circa 1936-1990
    - Macdougall, Allan, 1953
    - MacDowell Colony, 1967-1997, undated
    - MacIver, Loren, 1988
    - Mack, Maynard, 1965-1989
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1966
    - Macleod, Norman, 1981-1985
    - Maliszewski, William Murdoch, 1970, undated
    - McAlmon, Robert, 1949-1953
    - McBride, Henry, 1951-1962, undated
    - McCarthy, William H., Jr., 1938-1962
    - McClatchy, J. D., 1982, undated
    - McGinnis, John H., 1938-1951
    - McKelvie, Ian, 1975-1994
    - McLuhan, Marshall, 1970, undated
    - Manwaring, Elizabeth, 1932-1949, undated (Box 49)
    - March, Fredric, 1956
    - Marinetti, Luce, circa 1983-1996
    - Martin, Jean-Claude, 1968-1974, undated
    - Martin, H. Bradley, undated
    - Martinelli, Sheri, 1981-1987, undated; 4
    - Martz, Louis, 1937-1997, undated
    - Massey, Raymond, 1978 October 28
    - Materer, Timothy, 1983-1990, undated
    - Mathews, Elkin, 1936-1967, undated
    - Matthiessen, F. O., 1937
    - Mattingly, Ignatius, 1947, undated
    - Maurer, Alfred H., 1953, undated
    - Mauriber, Saul, 1950-1970
    - Mayer, Grace M., 1950-1980
    - Maynard, Theodore, 1936, undated
    - Mayor Gallery, 1950-1951
    - Mellon, Paul, 1997 March 4
    - Mellow, James R., 1967-1999
    - Mendelson, Edward, 1968-1982
    - Michigan State, 1969-1973
    - Miles, Walter R., 1949-1960, undated
    - Miller, Don, 1984-1993, undated
    - Miłosz, Czesław, 1946-1947, undated
    - Moore, Lamont & Henrietta, 1951-1993, undated
    - Moore, Marianne, 1952-1997, undated; 5
    - Morley, Christopher, undated
    - Morrill & Son, 1949-1994, undated
    - Morrow, Bradford, 1976-1984, undated
    - Mortlake, Harold, 1962-1965
    - Mott, Howard & Phyllis, 1974-1986
    - Munby, Anthony N. L., 1969-1987
    - Munger, Gertrude T., 1940-1953 (Box 50)
    - Murdock, Jan Nichols, circa 1975-1999
    - Mory's, 1988-2000
    - Murillo, Jorge, undated
    - Murphy, Ray L., undated
    - Museum of Modern Art, 1946-1990
    - Myers & Co., 1955-1976
    - "N" General, 1947-1995, undated
    - Nagy, Christophe de, 1962-1971, undated
    - Nardi, Marcia, 1981
    - Mason Trading Co., 1959
    - Nathan, Robert, 1968, undated
    - Nathanson, Richard, 1972-1975
    - Nejad, circa 1949-1979
    - Nesheim, Kenneth, 1969-1996
    - Neufeld, Philip, circa 1966-1990
    - New Directions, 1957-1999
    - New York Public Library, 1987-1997
    - Newnham, Anthony, 1956-1967
    - Newsweek, 1971-1972, undated
    - Nichol, Smith, undated
    - Nin, Anaïs, 1952
    - Norman, Dorothy, 1969-1997
    - Norman, Jeremy, 1973
    - "O" General, 1957-1990, undated
    - Ochsenfarth, Margaret & Jürgen, 1974-1988
    - Okala, Ollie Jewel Sims, circa 1980-1992
    - O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1971-1972, undated; 4
    - O'Neil, F. J., 1977-1998 (Box 51)
    - O'Neill, Carlotta, 1955-1993, undated; 7
    - O'Neill, Eugene
      - Foreword for Hart Crane's White Buildings, undated
      - "The Calm of Capricorn", 1972, undated
      - Work Diary, undated
      - Adato, Perry Miller, 1982-1984, undated
      - Aronberg, Winfield E., 1967-1969
      - Black, Stephen A., 1986-1995, undated
      - Butler, Henry, 1982-1985
      - Cerf, Bennett, undated
      - Kishi, Masayuki, 1991-1992, undated
      - Laufer, Beatrice, 1980, undated
      - Manheim, Michael, 1995-1999, undated
      - Maufort, Marc, 1982-1986
      - Miller, Ronald R., 1982-1989, undated
      - Ranald, Margaret L., 1985-1991
      - Rogers, Brian, 1997-1998, undated
      - Wylie, Max, 1970-1990
      - Unsorted correspondence, 1967-1990, undated
      - Photographs, undated
      - Unsorted writings, undated
      - Newsletter, 1984-1995
      - "O'Neills Plans for the Cycle", undated
      - The Monte Christo Cottage, 1983-1997, undated
      - Stockholm, 1988; 3 (Box 52)
      - The Eugene O'Neill Foundation, 1994-1997, undated
      - The Eugene O'Neill Review, 1985-1993, undated
      - The Eugene O'Neill Theatre Center, 1985-1997, undated
      - O'Neill conference, 1994-1995
    - Opplinger, Martin, 1948-1949, undated
    - Osborn, James M., 1954-1968, undated
    - Osborn, Robert & Elodie, 1980-1993
    - Osburn, Dorothy, 1940-1985; 4; (includes 1 10" record album)
    - Oxford University Press, 1937-1992
    - "P" General, 1941-1988, undated
    - Pacifici, Sergio, 1961, undated
    - Padgette, Paul, 1967-1999, undated
    - Pagany Magazine, 1970 March 3
    - Paideuma, 1971-1985; 3
    - Paideuma, 1986-1997 (Box 53)
    - Parker & Son, Ltd., 1955-1969
    - Parks, Steven, 1961-1985, undated
    - Partington, Paul, 1989-1990, undated
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1962-1994, undated; 2
    - Pennsylvania, 1962, undated
    - Peterson, Dorothy, 1955, undated
    - Peyre, Henri, 1988
    - Pharos Books, 1983-1995; 5
    - Pivano, Fernanda, 1964-1967, undated
    - P. J. & A. E. Dobell, Booksellers, 1943-1966
    - Plank, George, 1949, undated
    - Pollock, Helen Channing, 1947-1960, undated
    - Porter, José, 1947-1951, undated
    - Pottle, Fred, 1947-1950
    - Pound, Dorothy, 1962-1972, undated
    - Pound, Ezra
      - Correspondence of Donald Gallup regarding Ezra Pound
        - Booksellers
          - "A - Z" General, 1967-1994, undated
        - Individuals
          - "A - Z" General, circa 1962-1994; 2
          - Ardizzone, Maria Luisa, 1988-1996
          - Bacigalupo, Massimo, 1983-1996
          - Bauman, Walter, 1995
          - Bedford, Agnes, 1957-1968, undated
          - Bose, Buddhadeva, 1962, undated
          - Bucktrout, Daisy, 1964-1965
          - Cookson, William, 1970
          - Fisher, Margaret, 1998-2000
          - French, William, 1984-1988
          - Garcia Terres, Jaime, 1959-1962 (Box 54)
          - Hughes, Robert, 1994-2000; 1 folder, 1 computer disk
          - Ivancich, Gianfranco, 1978-1981, undated
          - Kodama, Sanehide, 1970-1985, undated
          - Kostetzky, Eaghor G., 1962-1963
          - Manning, Frederic, 1977 December 21
          - Meacham, H. M., 1963-1972
          - Merker, K. K., 1992-1995
          - Mitchell, Breon, 1983-1984, undated
          - Miyake, Akiko, 1986-1996, undated; 2
          - Moore, Arthur V., 1961-1963
          - Nadel, Ira R., 1988-1992
          - Newberry, Samuel David, 1962, undated
          - Niemojowski, Jerzy K., 1961-1962
          - Norman, Charles, 1970
          - Rainey, Lawrence S., 1989 September 28
          - Robbins, J. Albert, 1962
          - Schafer, Murray, 1962-1970, undated
          - Seyersted, Brita, 1981, undated
          - Takata, Tomiichi, 1981-1987, undated
          - Taylor, Richard, 1982-1999
          - Wood, Florence, 1957-1962, undated
        - Libraries
          - "A - Z" General, 1962-1985, undated
          - Trinity College Library, 1963, undated
          - Yale Archive, undated
        - Publishers
          - "A - Z" General, 1952-1990, undated; 2
          - Anacapa Books, 1979-1980
          - Bel Esprit, undated
          - L'Herne, 1963-1967, undated
          - Majno, Luigi, 1975-1977, undated
      - Transcripts, photostats, photocopies, and publications of Ezra Pound correspondence
        - Aiken, Conrad, undated
        - Bennett, Arnold, undated
        - Binyon, Laurence, undated
        - Brodzky, Horace, undated
        - Buss, Kate, undated
        - Canfield, undated
        - Carter, W., undated
        - Chicago Tribune, 1982, undated
        - Chute, Desmond, undated
        - Covici, Pascal & Friede, Donald S., undated
        - Cunard, Nancy, undated
        - Dulac, Helen, undated
        - Eliot, T. S., undated
        - Faber & Gwyer Ltd., undated
        - Friede, Donald S., undated
        - Gallup, Donald, undated
        - Gingrich, Arnold, undated
        - Harding, E. A. F., 1955, undated
        - Jepson, Edgar, undated (Box 55)
        - Jordan, Viola, undated
        - Lane, John, 1963, undated
        - Laughlin, Jay, undated
        - Lewis, Wyndham & Bedford, Agnes, 1983
        - Mathews, Elkin, undated
        - Meacham, H. M., undated
        - Mencken, H. L., undated
        - Monroe, Harriet, undated
        - Murakami, undated
        - Newbolt, Henry, undated
        - Ogden, C. K., undated